Preliminary Inventory of the John M. Bennett Correspondence, 1969-2017 SPEC.RARE.CMS.0171
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Correspondence received B, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 317)
- Correspondence received B, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 319)
- Correspondence received C, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 320)
- Correspondence received C, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 321)
- Correspondence received D, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 322)
- Correspondence received E, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 323)
- Correspondence received E, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 324)
- Correspondence received F, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 325)
- Correspondence received F, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 326)
- Correspondence received F, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 327)
- Correspondence received G, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 328)
- Correspondence received G, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 329)
- Correspondence received H, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 330)
- Correspondence received H, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 331)
- Correspondence received H, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 332)
- Correspondence received I, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 333)
- Correspondence received J, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 334)
- Correspondence received J, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 335)
- Correspondence received K, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 336)
- Correspondence received K, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 337)
- Correspondence received K, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 338)
- Correspondence received K, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 339)
- Correspondence received L, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 340)
- Correspondence received L, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 341)
- Correspondence received L, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 342)
- Correspondence received M, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 343)
- Correspondence received M, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 344)
- Correspondence received M, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 345)
- Correspondence received N, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 346)
- Correspondence received O, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 347)
- Correspondence received P, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 348)
- Correspondence received R, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 349)
- Correspondence received R, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 350)
- Correspondence received S, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 351)
- Correspondence received S, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 352)
- Correspondence received S, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 353)
- Correspondence received T, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 354)
- Correspondence received U, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 355)
- Correspondence received V, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 356)
- Correspondence received V, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 357)
- Correspondence received V, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 358)
- Correspondence received V, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 359)
- Correspondence received V, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 360)
- Correspondence received W, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 361)
- Correspondence received W, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 362)
- Correspondence received W, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 363)
- Correspondence received Y, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 364)
- Correspondence, Undated (Box 94)
- Correspondence, Undated (Box 95)
- Correspondence, Undated (Box 96)
- Mail Art, Undated (Box 97)
- Correspondence K-Z, 2013 (Box 98)
- Correspondence, 2011 (Box 99)
- Correspondence A-J, 2013 (Box 100)
- Correspondence R-Z, 2011 (Box 101)
- Correspondence and publications, 2010-2011 (Box 102)
- Correspondence, 2011-2012 (Box 103)
- Correspondence and publications, 2015-2013 (Box 104)
- Correspondence and poetry, 2012 (Box 105)
- Correspondence and publications, 2010 (Box 106)
  Contains compact disks.
- Correspondence and publications, 2012 (Box 107)
  Contains compact discs.
- Correspondence and publications, 2012 (Box 108)
- Correspondence A-Q, 2011 (Box 109)
- Correspondence, Undated (Box 110)
- Mail Art, Undated (Box 111)
- Mail Art, Undated (Box 112)
- Mail Art from Mike Dyar, 2013 (Box 113)
- Mail art from Mike Dyar, 2012-2014 (Box 114)
- Mail art from Mike Dyar, 2012-2014 (Box 115)
- Email correspondence with Richard Kostelanetz, 2014 December 18-19, 2015 June 26-27 (Box 116)
- Correspondence A-L, 2014 (Box 117)
- Correspondence M-Z, 2014 (Box 118)
- Sculptures and mail art from Mike Dyer, 1995, 2014-2015 (Box 119)
- Correspondence with Jim Bennett and Ficus strangulensis, 1995-2008 (Box 120)
- Mail art, video recordings, and computer files, 1994-2010 (Box 121)
  VHS videocassettes; color; sound; approximate run time: unknown; Compacts discs; approximate run time: unknown
- Accession No. RARE.2016.0058, 1969-2016; 4.07 Cubic feet
  - Correspondence A, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence B, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence B (2), Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence C, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence D, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence E, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence F, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence F (2), Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence G, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence H, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.001)
  - Correspondence I, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence J, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence K, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence L, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence M, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence M (2), Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence N, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence O, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence P, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence Q-R, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence S, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence S (2), Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence T, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence U, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence V, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence W, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Correspondence X, Y, Z, Undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.002)
  - Postcards to and from the Bennett family, 1970s-1980s (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Family correspondence, 1980s (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Family correspondence, 1980s (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Mail art envelop, 1996 (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Poems, 1969-1970 (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Poems and writings, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Bennett (John) various forms of artwork, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Collages, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Collages and poems from Texas Fontanella, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - A Sculpture With an Untold Story, 2015 July (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.005)
  - Collages, trashpo, visual poetry, and art from Texas Fontanella (3) folders, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.003)
  - Trashpo from Texas Fontanella, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.004)
  - Tube art sent to John Bennett, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.004)
  - Oversize mail art, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2016.0058.004)
- Accession No. RARE.2017.0037, 2015-2017; 4.2 Cubic feet
  Scope and Contents
  Contains various correspondence sent both to John Bennett and New Luna Bisonte. Also includes collections of poetry, art, collages,or materials related to collages.
  - Correspondence A, 2015-2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence B, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence B (2), 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence B (3), 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence B (4), 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence C, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Tom Cassidy-The Impossibilists, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence D, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence E, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence F, 2016
  - Correspondence G, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence G (2), 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.001)
  - Correspondence H, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
    1 compact disc
  - Correspondence I, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence J, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence K, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence L, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence M, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence M (2), 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence N, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence O, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - PADW, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence P, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence Q-R, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence S, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence S (2), 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence T, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.002)
  - Correspondence U, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Correspondence V, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Correspondence W, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Correspondence XYZ, 2016 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Up to the Both April, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Collage and art material from Australia, 2017 March (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Skull related correspondence from Lomita, California, 2017 September (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Sparkly silver skull sent from Jennifer Weigel, 2016 November (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.003)
  - Fontanella (Texas) collage materials sent to John M. Bennett, 2016 July (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.004)
  - Fontanella (Texas) 70 collage materials sent to John M. Bennett, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.004)
  - 11 manila folders containing collage materials, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.004)
  - Collage materials from Vittore Baroni/Le Forbici di Manitu, 2017 August (Box Accession No. RARE.2017.0037.004)
- Accession No. RARE.2018.0086, 2017; 3.98 Cubic feet
  Arrangement of Materials
  This addition is unprocessed; materials are arranged in the order received.
  Contains correspondence sent to and from John M. Bennett from other Avant writers including Ivan Arguelles. In addition, contains mail art correspondence pieces and poetry mailed to Bennett.
  - Ivan Arguelles & JMB, 2017 March-May (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Ivan Arguelles & JMB, 2017 June-July (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Ivan Arguelles & JMB, 2017 August-September (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Ivan Arguelles & JMB, 2017 October-November (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Ivan Arguelles & JMB, 2017 December (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence A, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence B (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence B (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence B (3), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence C (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence C (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence D (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence D (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence E, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence F (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence F (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence F (3), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence G (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence G (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)
  - Correspondence G (3), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence H, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence I, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence J, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence K, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence L (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence L (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence M (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence M (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence M (3), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence M (4), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence N, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence O, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence P (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence P (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence Q-R, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence S (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence S (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence T, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence U, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.002)
  - Correspondence V, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Correspondence W (1), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Correspondence W (2), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Correspondence X-Y-Z, 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Let Me Tell You About My Dream, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Miscellanea, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Writings of Winstead Macario, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Writings of Jose Primitiro, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Poemas Dedicatorios, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.003)
  - Fontanella, Texas: Collage poems (8), 2017 (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.004)
  - Shumel: Glove, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.005, Item 1)
  - Cracker Jack Kid: Perseids Shower, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.005, Item 2)
  - Postcard with sea shells, undated (Box Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.006)
  - The 70 project, undated (Folder Accession No. RARE.2018.0086.001)